Suddenly Explorers!
Suddenly explorers!
Minna! Minna no Gorogoro Starlust! Suddenly Talks Announce! Hello!
I'm Karen Tachibana and Hinano Sakura!
Please join us!
We are the Suddenly Explorers!
Yes! We are the expedition!
Today we have Karen and Hinano!
Hey, can we decide who's the best?
What?
Why don't we decide who's the best explorer of Inari Expedition?
I was thinking, we should decide who's the best.
You've been thinking that?
It's that time of the year.
Today, I'd like you two to play an original game.
After deciding on the best game, we'll go to one of the stores in the museum and challenge them to a fight with that game.
Before we go, why don't we fight and decide who is the best?
There are two games.
Let's play the first game.
The first game is
KOKON East-West game with 3 imaginary characters.
There is a game called “Kocon East-West”, isn't there?
The red one is like a pan-pan post-pan-pan tomato.
You say them in order to the rhythm.
If you make a mistake or can't keep up the rhythm, you lose.
In this game, you have to say three fictitious three-letter words.
Three-letter words
You take turns saying three fictitious three-letter words that don't exist in the world.
You may not be able to say this one either.
If you can't say this one, or if you get stuck or say the word that came up once, you lose.
I see. It's difficult.
It's more of a vocabulary game, or how fast you can think.
If you were to play east-west, you'd be at a disadvantage.
It's okay to be angry.
That's not true.
You're not used to this.
Here's the first game.
You'll be fine. It's okay.
Which one do you want to go first? First offensive.
General, let's play rock-paper-scissors!
Okay, we'll start with Karen.
Three imaginary characters starting with Karen.
This is an east-west game
Pan-pan~!
Yes, sir.
Are you okay?
You understand it, right?
Well, let's just try it once.
This is just like practice.
You'll have to compete with the waiter for the real thing.
Demonstration.
I just want to see who's good.
Then, let's use Mr. Curry's timing.
Okay.
Well then...
Out of this world.
From the past to the present.
Hmm?
Out-of-this-world words.
Three letters.
Three-letter word game.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ready?
Pan-pan
Ponit
Luns
Myoo-myo!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What did you say?
Myoo-myo.
How many letters are in the word myoumyou?
Uh-oh.
Weak.
Six. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you going to do? I'm too small a fish to be a good one, but I'm on the same level as him.
Myung-myung, myung-myung, that's understandable, but it's weird.
Why did he repeat himself?
I'll only do it once more... so get up and do it again!
Why is it so strange that there's a split in the distance?
Why is it so weak?
I've never done it before in my life... but I'm still waiting for a human to enter the room... so I'm really scared...
I'm sorry. It's the cat's nekkunini.
I'll start with my own house, Karen.
Then let's return it at the time of the evacuation.
Chins, what's up?
Lunka, Matsuno!
Yunsu, Mariko...
Mariko's here?
There's something fishy one or two doors down.
She's talking like Joon-su?
Yoon-su?
Did you say Yoon-su?
No Joon-su?
But there's Mariko.
But there might be Joon-su.
Yoon-su is also Korean.
If you do a search, you might be able to find that.
It's hard to tell.
But there's Mariko.
Mariko's there. She's so weak.
You're so weak, Karen.
Is this okay when you fight with the waiter outside?
I'm sure it's fine if I slow down a bit and set a better pace.
A slower pace, you could say.
Okay, Karen, let's start with the slow version.
Any speed you want.
Here we go.
I'm going to say it.
Gonko.
Masanao
Minta
Venta Bento
Culture!
Watch out! No one will notice!
What if no one finds out?
If no one finds out, it's OK, but it's still clean!
It's a good image!
Self-reported!
Good!
I don't know if I can say intonation is a culture!
I think I can go.
I've been watching you too closely, Karen, and I'm not watching Hinano enough!
I'm sure I'll make a mistake! I'm sure I'll make a mistake!
I was suspicious of Matsuna, though.
I'm telling you the truth!
Matsuna is cheating with her intonation.
Anyway, I'm going to call this first game a convincing win for Ms. Hinano.
The real work begins now!
Is it enough to beat the waiter?
That's the point!
Game 2 is here!
Super face-off!
What the hell is that?
What?
There's a game called “Away, That Way” that I'm sure everyone has played at one time or another.
I think everyone has played this game before, but this time, I'm going to try a special move for this game.
I've come up with the special moves!
The special moves are written in this box.
Before you fight in the game, you draw the special move card.
Before you fight, you draw a special move card and use the special move card to fight.
I see.
It's a little difficult to think about, so I think it's better if you try it.
Yes.
Then, please draw two special move cards from the box.
Yes, sir.
This special move will make a big difference.
Here you go.
Wow, it's strong! Phoenix and Triple!Wow, it's strong! Phoenix and Triple!
For our viewers, Triple is a special move that allows you to attack three times in a row when you attack with the “Hoi, hoi, hoi.
Strong. You mean like Hoi, hoi, hoi?
It's a very strong card. Phoenix.
This is a phoenix. Even if it is defeated once, it can revive.
You mean you have two of them? You have two of them. Say “Wow!” and come back to life.
This is Hinano-san's special move card. Karen, please announce your special move card.
Oh! Double and Center Breakthrough. Double is a slightly weaker version of Triple. Double means you can attack twice.
The center breakthrough is a defensive move, usually avoided by going up, left, right, down...
Head? I see. Please use these two special moves to face each other.
I see.
Then let's do it right away.
Let's go!
Go away, go away, go away!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
You're too eager to use your special move!
No one uses it.
But he's fast!
Failed to break through the center.
You failed to break through the center.
What was that?
I didn't expect my attack.
Failed.
Did you get it like this?
It's difficult.
Not good?
Let's try one more time.
I'll change it up.
Okay.
Lupin the Skill and Left Right.
You already know Hinano-san's.
Double and Phoenix.
You already know the technique, don't you?
Karen-san's
Left Right is when your opponent is on the defensive.
When they're on the defensive, you can only turn left and right.
I see.
When Hinano-san's on defense... When Hinano-san is on defense
I can only see left and right.
Oh no, and Lupin and Skill, this can steal one of Hinano-san's special moves in Lupin's favor.
Enough which one is better which one is better
I'm going to eat.
Who has a coach? Who has a coach? Who has a coach? Who has a second?
It's not fair. Foul play. Who did you bring?
This is the tournament? I thought for sure I'd get Phoenix.
I thought I had an advantage with the double, but then the outing, and the second, he came with me.
It's a diplomatic battle, Mr. Inano, but there are two terms, and all you have to do is win.
You just have to keep winning. Are you okay? Can you remember? Yes, I can.
Right and left here. That's right, Mr. Inano, right and left are the only ways.
Let's do our best. It'll be cool if we win. Let's do it.
Let's do it. Let's go for the second round. Use your special moves and win.
saya kuja kebay, Digital
Situation. Recording.
Phoenix is the best.
The Phoenix is the best.
This is the Phoenix.
Phoenix is the strongest.
If he's strong, Phoenix might be strong.
You can use it to revive him.
Maybe.
And the other thing is that Karen is simply a weak giver.
She wants you to turn around and look the other way.
That could be it.
Now that would be a super Aikido game.
I see.
At any rate, here we have Hinano-san winning two in a row.
You're the ace of the expedition.
For now, as the game ace.
I'm going to challenge a certain store to a game.
Let's go get some points that will give our viewers a good deal.
I see.
Let's make the showdown look like a showdown.
If we lose the whole thing...
Oh, no. Oh, no.
For all of you.
We have to win, right?
Yeah. - Yeah.
Then let's go challenge the store to a game.
Let's go.
We've moved to the garden terrace on the fourth floor. And our opponent for the first match is Nanami from Rooftop e-Garden on the fourth floor.
Thank you very much.
This is a showdown, so the mood is a little bit friendly.
We're going to do it with a lot of energy.
We're going to give a special prize to the viewers who watch the video if they buy the product, so we're going to do our best to make it happen.
I'd like to start with the first battle, the battle of the three fictitious characters.
Let's start with the first battle, the three imaginary letters.
I have already explained the rules to you, Nami.
Nami, who would you like to fight?
Well then...
Ha-ha-ha.
You're so perceptive.
She sees right through me.
Then beat her, Karen.
I'll do my best.
Then let's go at your own time, Karen.
Three-letter word, out-of-this-world kokon, east-west game.
Yay!
Poof!
Nepoko!
Numora.
Pan Pan
Yoina
pan
Pan!
Hanuki
Pan-pan!
Miyotko.
Miyotko?
Uh-huh?
Yes, yes!
What did you just say? What did you just say?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Miyoko?
Hanukin.
What's Hanukin?
I've heard of Hanukin.
What's that?
A chick?
In the muck of history?
Are you sure you're all right?
One more time.
Shall we start with Nanami?
Let's start with Nanami.
Three, two, one.
It's in the tree of heaven.
I pulled it out again.
Pulled it out?
I tend to pull it out!
Nanami, I'm pulling out!
I pulled out my teeth and my hand.
I'm scared!
He's a psychopath!
He's destroying the human body.
Cutting teeth, cutting corners.
You can't cut corners on the job.
Oh, of course not.
Okay, then.
Let's call the first game, and let's call it a win for the expedition team.
Is that okay?
No, that's a win.
Yes!
Thank you!
Yay!
Okay, let's see if I got a point here.
You got it.
The game is on. In case you're wondering, there's a game.
There's one more game.
Nami and Hinano are going to play an exhibition match.
and Hinano-san in an exhibition match.
Why don't we do it?
Super face-off!
It's a showdown.
This one, too.
I've already explained the rules to Nami
I've already explained the rules to Nami.
Let's get on with the battle!
First of all, please draw a special move card
First of all, please draw a special move card.
Open!
Max Whiffle Triple!
Oh, man!
Triple is
Three attacks in a row.
Strong indeed!
Max Hoi Hoi
This one goes that way.
Max, I'll have you go all out with the tension!
Isn't this the weakest one?
He's so excited, he looks so strong.
If you don't look excited, you've already lost.
I'm not shy or anything.
Look at the tension I'm feeling right now.
Are you in it?
Yes, I'm in it.
I don't know anyone like that.
Let's see your special move, Nami.
Which one?
This one.
Oh, man.
What about the double?
Oh, no!
That's not good!
Double, double, double.Double attacked twice.
And here comes the lupin and the skill.
I might pull a Max whiffle, you know.
I might steal Max Hui Hui, you know.
What should I do! Kate, help me!
What shall we do? Nanami.
Which one?
Right, right! That's right.
He's just a very excited person.
You, this time.
Why are you doing this? It's funny.
I got a double and a triple.
I'm going to activate the triple.
I see!
Five times is not good enough.
But, Hina-san...
All you have to do is win.
You can do it! You'll see a miracle!
If you have to stay at Max's...
Then let's go to the showdown.
Hinano-san vs.
Hinano-san vs. Yanami-san
Let's start!
Station goo!
Yes! Codition!
Turn around!
Aaahhh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
I lost!
And if anything, Nanami was more excited than me.
Why?
Ms. Hinano lost this game, but Ms. Karen won the first game, so I'd like to get a point from her.
I'd like to get some points from Nami. What can I get?
We'd like to give away soft drinks to the first 20 people who watch this video.
Yay, MAX whiz! Yay, max whip!
Are you sure?
Yes!
Thank you very much.
If you saw this video, please come to the rooftop e-garden on the 4th floor. We'll be waiting for you.
We'll be waiting for you.
Thank you very much, Nami.
Thank you very much.
It was fun!
Let's go to the next battle!
The next battle is the one that is currently being held on the 4th floor of e-Beans.
Mr. Kato from Hohjimari Production Studio, who is currently holding a festival on the 4th floor of eBeans!
Mr. Kato, nice to meet you!
Pleased to meet you.
What? Kato!
Kato.
We're good friends.
Karen is.
That's right.
She sells samples for the staff.
I went to Yamagata to buy some samples privately, and one of my fans heard about it and asked me to come to eBeans, so I did.
I'm so happy!
We can even have a showdown this time.
You've come here several times for private shopping, haven't you?
We've had a lot of inquiries from fans.
Karen mentioned rings and earrings.
I heard that someone saw it and looked it up.
They searched for Yamagata Strawberry staff samples and found that we came up.
I see.
We've been getting a lot of inquiries.
What?
So I made an inquiry after hearing from an eBeans fan.
At first, I really thought I'd be turned away at the door.
It's a one-day event in front of Sendai Station.
They were very easy to get in touch with.
I see.I see.
That's what I was talking about.
I couldn't have done it without you, Karen.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
So, I guess you're going to have to lose today.
Well, thank you very much, I'll do my best.
Well then, let's move on to the showdown.
It's Ms. Kato versus Karen.
Let's start by choosing a special move.
You have a special move?
Yes! Yes, there is!
You can use the moves written on the card, not the usual “Look over there”.
Don't worry, Mr. Kato, you can do it.
Phoenix can revive once even if he loses the game with “Look away, look up!
Like a phoenix that can revive once.
That's nice.
What is “paradasing”?
It's a game of rock, paper, scissors where Karen can't play par.
Foo or choki? - Foo and choki.
Karen can only play foo and chokes.
This is the best deck.
The best deck.
We've got to win this.
You're right... it's Karen's deck.
That's right.
First one.
Then!
A-ha!
Hey!
What's this?
Hey, Max!
What is it?
It's a card that says you're always in a max tension while you're looking over there.
It's a card that is always in a high state of tension.
The other one is...
Another one!
Double! Double!
I can do it twice.
It can attack twice... twice... and twice.
I see.
Okay?
Yes, sir.
First one is “Goo”?
Let's start with “goo”.
Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Look away, look away, look away!
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
Let's do it!
First, goo.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Face away, face away!
ah, ah, ah, ah
ah!
Pooh!
I'm going to make par, right?
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
It's cold.
Cold.
I've been doing this all day with no par.
No par all the way.
We're losing on penalties.
What's this?
Gentle.Gentle
No. 2 man to man
No. 2 man to the return of the year
I got something on me
There's a phrase in his hair.
That's a little...
Karen... that's a bit much.
What are you going to do about the special move?
Maybe we should ask them to redraw the lots.
That's fine.
Leave it as it is.
That makes you stronger, Kato-san.
I'm stronger?
I was just suggesting we draw again.
Karen is at a disadvantage.
If we continue as is...
She's the strongest.
She's just an ogre.
An ogre.
Wada-chan's a demon!
It's a “kanreki” demon!
I'm scared.
What do you think?
You mean we'll reset it once?
Reset.
Two cards.
Thank you.
Double.
Two acts.
from ?
Boooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
Tension is high.
If you see this as not being tensioned, you're going to lose.
Karen, I'll do my best!
I got a double!
Change hoi!
Change hoi is the original version of the “hoi” part of the “that way” part of the “that way” part of the “hoi” part.
It means you're the weakest. It means he's the weakest.
It's a stupid special move.
This is going to be one hell of a fight.
We both have doubles.
Kato-san has Max Hui Hui.
Karen has Change Hui Hui.
They're almost even.
In terms of special moves...
Interesting!
Goo at first!
It's OK!
It's great!
You lost!
First goo!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Turn around!
You don't have the heart for a joke!
Mr. Kato, first of all, you were wonderful!
Really great!
I'm here for real!
Perfect!
But Karen is a change-hoi.
She said “janken nyoyo”!
She should have said “turn around and say ‘nyo yyo’”!
She said “janken nyo yyo”!
I changed that too!
It was the third day of the game, and I was at my limit!
But Karen, you won!
It was kindness!
Kindness!
You managed to save the win!
That's great!
What you said earlier...
Even though you scored a point May I have your score?
May I have your score?
Thank you very much.
I'm glad to hear that the next one is coming up.
About EB
July!
From July 12!
We have about a month
We're going to have a meeting.
You'll be there for a month?
Really?
You're going to turn your head that way!
He's already looking this way!
Turn around!
I'll do it!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Please come!
Please come and watch the show!
Thank you very much!
Today, we had a match between The Rooftop e-Garden and Gochinmari Seisakukoubou to decide who is the best!
It was a great battle!
We were able to beat both of them and got great scores!
Karen won both of them, though.
Kato-san took it all, though.
That was the best!
In a way, it was the best.
It was fun.
It was a wonderful encounter.
Thank you very much.
I hope you will come to eBees and enjoy the scores and all.
I hope you will watch this video and compete in the heaping.
So, today's exploration was who is the strongest?
That was the title.
Thank you very much!
Bye bye! indecent